var questions = [
    { type: "OX", question: "1+1은 2이다.", correctAnswer: "O" },
    { type: "OX", question: "2+2은 5이다.", correctAnswer: "X" },
    { type: "multiple", question: "1+1의 결과는?", choices: ["1", "2", "3"], correctAnswer: "2" },
    { type: "multiple", question: "가장 큰 수는?", choices: ["7", "5", "9"], correctAnswer: "9" },
    { type: "short", question: "3+2는?", correctAnswer: "5" },
    { type: "OX", question: "1+1은 2이다.", correctAnswer: "O" },
    { type: "OX", question: "2+2은 5이다.", correctAnswer: "X" },
    { type: "multiple", question: "1+1의 결과는?", choices: ["1", "2", "3"], correctAnswer: "2" },
    { type: "multiple", question: "가장 큰 수는?", choices: ["7", "5", "9"], correctAnswer: "9" },
    { type: "short", question: "3+2는?", correctAnswer: "5" }
];